Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers - Photographs
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series I: Governor’s Papers
  - Groups, Meetings, Events
    - Committee on Employment of the Handicapped – Photo with Miss Wheelchair America and Miss Wheelchair Tennessee (Box 44)
    - Democratic Executive Caucus (Box 44)
    - Extra Mile Photographs (2 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Media Availability, Rogers Press Conference (Box 44)
    - Republican Eagles, The American Club, July 1997 (Box 44)
    - Republican Legislators (Box 44)
    - Republican Women (Box 44)
    - Red Tape Cutters (2 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Republican Neighborhood Meeting (2 Folders) (Box 44)
    - RNM with Mayor Susan Weiner (3 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Sunset Symphony – Newspaper copies (Box 44)
    - Teletune Gorilla (Box 44)
    - Tennessee Film, Tape, Music Commission (Box 44)
    - Tennessee Tomorrow (2 Folders) (Box 44)
    - Tennessee Seniors – Knowles Center (Box 44)
    - University of Tennessee Board of Trustees - Swearing in (Box 44)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Places, Events
    - Carter County – Hanging Tree Gavel Memento (Box 45)
    - Columbia – Mule Day (Box 45)
    - Cosby – Ramp Festival (Box 45)
    - Lawrenceburg (Box 45)
    - Knoxville – Dogwood Festival (Box 45)
    - Sevierville – Bean Supper (Box 45)
    - Smithville – Fiddlers Convention (Box 45)
    - Andrew Johnson Bust Dedication (Box 45)
    - Capitol Hill Tree Planting and Cannon (Box 45)
    - Capitol Building Photos (Box 45)
    - Clinch River Breeder Reactor Project – Photo with Sponsors of the Resolution (Box 45)
    - Contract 18th Avenue Overpass – Lamar Alexander and Fulton (Box 45)
    - Easter Seal and Angel One (Box 45)
    - First Citizens Bank Anniversary (Box 45)
    - Flags (Box 45)
    - Food Services Manager – Residence (Box 45)
    - Football Game (Box 45)
    - Frog Jumping Contest, April 21, 1979 (Box 45)
    - Government Days – Mountain City High School (Box 45)
    - Kefauver Building Dedication (Box 45)
    - Meet the Press with Lamar Alexander, September 24, 1995 – Headshot (Box 45)
    - Metro Center Challenge Run – State Runners (2 Folders) (Box 45)
    - Picnic at the Residence – Families Alexander stayed with on his Campaign Walk, Minnie Pearl (Box 45)
    - Residence (Box 45)
    - Resolution – Press Release for Ernest J. Jones Bridge. No Photo (Box 45)
    - Sequoyah Nuclear Drill (Box 45)
    - State Dinner – Concert Pianist Allison Nelson and Daughter Elise Neal, Miss Tennessee (Box 45)
    - State Employee of the Month (Box 45)
    - Sure Shot Rabbit Supper, March 11, 1980 (Box 45)
    - Tennessee Performing Arts Center (Box 45)
    - TVA News Conference (Box 45)
    - WNGE Flag with Honey Alexander (Box 45)
    - Unidentified Event – Outdoor Festival (Box 45)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Lamar Alexander Headshots
    - Lamar Alexander – Early Photo (Box 46)
    - Lamar Alexander in Plaid Shirt – Leaning Against Tree (4 Folders) (Box 46)
    - Lamar Alexander in Red Flannel Shirt – Candid (4 Folders) (Box 46)
    - Lamar Alexander – Original Portrait as Governor (3 Folders) (Box 46)
    - Lamar Alexander – Black and White Photos as Governor (Box 46)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Lamar Alexander Headshots
    - Lamar Alexander – Governor (Entire Box) (Box 47)
  - Photographs, Arranged by Subject
  - Lamar Alexander Headshots
    - Lamar Alexander with Jacket Over Shoulder – President of University of Tennessee (3 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Lamar Alexander with Jacket On – President of University of Tennessee (5 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Lamar Alexander with Newspapers – President of University of Tennessee (2 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Lamar Alexander Headshot – President of University of Tennessee (2 Folders) (Box 48)
    - Lamar Alexander – Secretary of Education (Box 48)
    - Lamar Alexander – With Microphone (2 Folders) (Box 48)
  - Candid Shots and Miscellaneous Photos (20 Folders) (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Contact Sheets (7 Folders) (Box 50)
  - Slides and Negatives (Box 51)
    Film Rejects (3 Folders)
    Friends Slides
    Commissioners
    Mardi Gras
    Sunset Symphony
    Bruceton
    Columbia
    Fairview
    McMinnville
    Memphis
    Red Bank
    Rutherford County
    Tipton
    Wilson County
    Miscellaneous